http://www.the3marketers.com/privacy

Home
Solutions
SEARCH ENGINE OPTIMIZATION (SEO)
PAY-PER-CLICK ADVERTISING (PPC)
Solutions
SEARCH ENGINE OPTIMIZATION (SEO)
PAY-PER-CLICK ADVERTISING (PPC)
Privacy PolicyHome / Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for The Three Marketers Inc. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contacts from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.
Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (name, phone number, email address), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or web designer) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Google Analytics
We use Google Analytics on our website. This is a web analytics service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United-States
The use of Google Analytics enables us to track how popular our site is, record visitor trends over a period of time and help us optimise our site for conversions and usability. While we can see data gathered over a timeframe, we do not collect personal information. Any data collected by Google for the purposes of Google Analytics will be treated according to Google’s Privacy Policy,
Sharing
In some occasions, we partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share your website information (such ftp or CMS access credentials) that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
LinksThis website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at403-2303993 or via email info@www.the3marketers.com
FREE ONLINE MARKETING ESTIMATE
Interested inSearch Engine Optimization (SEO)Pay-Per-Click AdvertisingSocial MediaApp MarketingName *Monthly BudgetEmail *Website (www.)Phone *KeywordsYour Needs and GoalsWebsiteSubmit
The Three Marketers Inc
104-1240 Kensington Road NW
Suite #310
(By Appointment Only)
Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
© 2020 The Three Marketers. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
Start typing and press Enter to search
